SARAH THOMAS



itz.sarahj@gmail.com



Brampton, ON

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Highly motivated and enthusiastic professional writer with over 6 years of customer service experience that translates into a deep understanding of, and ability to meet, clients' diverse expectations and needs. The proven track record of academic excellence demonstrates exceptional communication and interpersonal skills with the ability to work both independently and as part of a team.

EDUCATION

York University | Toronto, ON

Bachelor of Arts

English & Professional Writing, Expected in May 2024

- 8.0 GPA
- Dean's List Honouree 2020-2023
- York University Entrance Scholarship Recipient

Relevant Courses

- AP/PRWR 2007: Rhetoric: Strategy and Application
- AP/PRWR 2006: Fundamentals of Editing
- AP/PRWR 4003: Organizational Writing Practicum
- AP/PRWR 4001: Digital Authoring Practicum

St. Marguerite d'Youville SS | Brampton, ON

High School Diploma (OSSD) obtained June 2020

- Grade 12 Academic Excellence Award Recipient for an overall average of over 90%
- Grade 12 Canadian Law Award Recipient for highest course average (98%)
- Grade 12 English Award Recipient for highest course average (95%)

SKILLS

- Highly proficient in utilizing the complete Microsoft Office Suite, Canva, WordPress, and CapCut to streamline workflows, improve productivity, and create professional documents, spreadsheets, presentations, and email communications.
- Proven track record of successful upselling strategies, consistently exceeding sales targets and driving revenue growth
- Experience working in high-pressure environments
- Exceptional organizational and timemanagement skills

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RECEPTIONIST

Spagnuolo Professional Corporation | September 2019 - January 2020

- Delivered administrative support to team members by making copies, sending faxes, organizing documents and rearranging schedules.
- Maintained daily calendars, set up appointments with clients and planned daily office events.
- Utilized various scanning hardware, computer programs, and applications to scan files and documents including PC Law, The Conveyancer, and Microsoft Excel.

NON-LEGAL SUMMER STUDENT

Blaney McMurtry LLP. | May 2022 - September 2022

- Proficient in preparing and processing notarial certificates with meticulous attention to detail, ensuring accuracy and compliance with legal requirements
- Skilled in handling photocopies efficiently, and maintaining organization and confidentiality of sensitive documents
- Exceptional drafting skills, capable of crafting professional letters with clarity and precision, enhancing communication effectiveness
- Expertise in efficiently preparing courier slips, ensuring prompt and reliable delivery of important documents and packages

SALES ASSOCIATE

The Shoe Company | September 2017 - October 2023

- Efficiently managed time and resources to consistently deliver exceptional customer service, even during demanding highvolume periods
- Consistently met and exceeded daily loyalty conversion objectives
- Retained product, service and company policy knowledge to serve as a resource for both coworkers and customers
- Carried out POS transactions by having engaged positively with each customer and providing professional and polite support
- Built and maintained relationships with peers and upper management to drive team success